-I'm sorry! -That is it!
-抱歉 -天啊,我受夠了
You barge in here and you don't knock?
你不敲門就闖進來?
You have no respect for privacy. No,you wait!
-難道你不尊重別人的隱私權? -不,你慢著
-Can I just say one thing? -What?!
-我能說一件事嗎? -什麼事?
That's a relatively open weave. I can still see...
這塊布編的非常松,我仍能看見…
...your nippular areas.
…你的胸脯
The One With The Boobies
六人行 第1季 第13集 看胸脯
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
Honey,tell them the story about your patient...
親愛的,告訴他們你的病人
...who thinks things are other things.
如何把事想成另一件事
When the phone rings and she takes a shower.
例如電話響時她就去洗澡
That's pretty much it.
差不多是那樣
-But you tell it really well,sweetie. -Thanks. Okay.
-但你說得很好 -謝謝
Now go away so we can talk about you.
快走開我們才能談你
Okay. I'll miss you.
好吧,我會想念你的
-lsn't he great? -He's cute. He likes you so much.
-他很不錯吧 -他好帥,也好像很喜歡你
I know. He's so sweet. And so complicated,you know?
我知道,他人很好,而且很複雜
And for a shrink, he's not too shrinky.
有點神經質,但是有又不是太神經質
Think you'll do it on his couch?
他會在沙發上做嗎?
I don't know. That's a little weird.
我不知道…有點奇怪
It's vinyl.
聚乙稀做的
Okay,you guys want anything else?
大家還想要別的嗎?
-Could I have? -We're all out. Anybody else?
-要,我要… -抱歉,賣完了,其他人呢?
Did I miss something?
我是否錯過某事?
No,she's still upset because I saw her boobies.
她很生氣因為我看見她的胸脯
What were you doing seeing her boobies?
你看她的胸脯幹嗎?
It was an accident. I wasn't across the street with a telescope.
那是意外,我可不是隔條街用望遠鏡偷看
Can we change the subject,please?
能換個話題嗎?
These aren't her "boobies." These are her breasts.
沒錯,因為那不是她的胸脯 而是她的胸部
Pheebs,I was hoping for more of a change.
菲比,我要的不只是改變字眼
I always liked "Bazoombas."
我向來喜歡「波濤洶湧」(俚語)
Gives them a Latin spin.
給他個拉丁旋轉
Can we drop this already,please?
我們放下這個不說了,好不好?
Why are you embarrassed? They were very nice boobies.
你為什麼要難為情呢? 它們確實是非常好看的胸脯
"Nice"? They were "nice"?
「好看」?他們很「好看」?
That's it? I mean,mittens are "nice."
就這樣?手套也很好看
Okay. Rock,hard place. Me.
我…左右為難
You're so funny!
你真逗
He's really funny.
他真的很逗
I wouldn't wanna be there when the laughter stops.
他不笑的時候,我也不想待在這兒
Whoa,back up there,sparky.
等等,回去上句
What did you mean by that?
那是什麼意思?
It seems that maybe you have intimacy issues...
你似乎有親密上的問題
...that you use your humor to keep people at a distance.
你用你的幽默和人保持距離
I mean,I just met you. I don't know you from Adam.
我才剛認識你,我從亞當那裡沒聽說過你
Only child,right?
獨子?
Parents divorced before you hit puberty.
母在你青春期前離婚?
-How did you know that? -It's textbook.
-你怎會知道? -你很典型
Hey,you guys. You all know my dad,right?
各位,喬伊.你們都認識我爸吧?
-How long are you in the city? -Two days. I got a job.
-打算在紐約待多久? -就幾天.我在市中心有工作
I'm better off staying with Joey...
我想和喬伊同住
...than going back and forth on the ferry.
比來回坐渡輪好
-I don't know this one. -This is my friend Roger.
-我沒見過他 -他是我朋友羅傑
-Good to meet you. -You too.
-幸會,羅傑 -彼此彼此
-What happened to the puppet guy? -Dad.
-玩布偶的那個怎麼了? -爸
Oh,excuse me. So,Ross,how's the wife?
抱歉,羅斯,你的太太呢?
0 for 2,huh?
兩人出局了?
Chandler,say something funny.
錢德,說點好笑的
I gotta go. Miss you too.
我得掛電話了,我也想你
-I love you,but it's getting late -Say hi. Hey,Ma.
-我愛你,但現在很晚了 -讓我向她打聲招呼
I made the appointment with Dr. Bassida and
我和包西達大夫約了時間
Excuse me?
什麼?
Did you know this isn't Ma?
你知道這不是媽嗎?
Her name's Ronni.
她叫羅妮
She's a pet mortician.
寵物殯葬業者
Sure.
當然
So,how long you been...?
你和她多久了…
Remember when you were a kid, I'd take you to the navy yard?
記得小時候我常帶你去海軍軍港看大船?
-Since then? -No,it's only been six years.
-從那時候就開始了? -不,才6年
I wanted you to think of a nice memory so you'd know I'm not a terrible guy.
我只想勾起你美好的回憶 讓你不會覺得我一直是個大爛人
-What are you doing? -Chopping garlic.
-你們在幹嘛? -切大蒜
You don't crush it?
你不是把他們壓碎的嗎?
You're having an affair, I chop garlic. It's a wacky world.
這是你的風格,我一向都是切的 真是個古怪的世界
Joe,you ever been in love?
喬伊,你愛過嗎?
-I don't know. -Then you haven't.
-我不知道 -那就是沒有
-You're burning tomatoes. -You're one to talk.
-你的蕃茄燒焦了 -別想轉移話題
Your dad's in love. The worst part is, it's with two different women.
喬,你老爸愛得無法自拔 最糟的是我愛兩個女人
Oh,man! Please tell me one of them is Ma.
拜託你告訴我其中一個是媽
Of course one of them's Ma. What's the matter with you?
當然其中一個是你媽,你是怎麼搞的?
It's like if you woke up and found out...
這就像你某天起床突然發現
...your dad leads this double life.
你爸是個雙面人
He's like actually some spy working for the ClA.
就像是為中情局工作的間諜
That'd be cool.
那一定很酷
This blows!
但這個很爛
Do you think Dad cheated?
你以為爸爸騙你嗎?
I don't think so. That would involve sex.
我沒有這麼想 過.那一定包括了性是不是
I'd like to think that our parents don't do that.
我更加趨向於認為我父母沒有那麼做
I know. Why can't parents just stay parents?
為何父母就不能是父母?
Why do they have to become people? Why do they have?
為何他們就得成為人間男女? 為何他們要?
Why...
為什麼…
...can't you stop staring at my breasts?
…別再盯著我的胸部看
What?
什麼?
Didn't you get a good enough look?
那一天你還看得不夠嗎?
We're all adults here. There's only one way to resolve this.
我們都已是成年人 此事只有一個解決之道
Since you saw her boobies you have to show her your pee-pee.
既然你看過她的胸脯 你應該讓她看你的小弟弟
You know, I don't see that happening.
辦不到
Come on. He's right. Tit for tat.
拜託,他說得對.以眼還眼
Well,I'm not showing you my tat!
我不會讓你看的
-It's Phoebe. -And Rog!
-是菲比 -還有羅傑!
Come on up.
快上來
Oh,good! Rog is here.
這下可好,羅傑來了
-What's the matter with Rog? -It's a little thing. I hate that guy!
-羅傑有什麼不對勁嗎? -沒什麼,小事.我討厭這傢伙
So he was a little analytical. That's what he does.
為什麼?因為他太善於分析 他就是這種人別這樣嘛
Come on,he's not that bad.
他沒那麼糟
You're wrong! Why would I marry her...
你錯了!如果當初我感覺到
...if I thought that she was a lesbian?
感覺到她是女同志我何必和她結婚呢?
I don't know. Maybe you wanted your marriage to fail.
我不知道,或許你想讓婚姻失敗
Why? Why would l? Why?
為什麼?我為什麼這樣?為什麼?
I don't know. Maybe low self-esteem?
我不知道,或許自信心不足
Maybe to compensate for overshadowing a sibling. Maybe
或許是彌補你讓你妹相形見絀的愧疚
Wait! Go back to that "sibling" thing.
或許…等等,回到妹妹的話題
Well,I don't know.
什麼?我不知道
You could've sabotaged your marriage...
你要使你的婚姻觸礁
...so the sibling would feel like less of a failure.
讓你妹在父母面前不那麼抬不起頭
That's ridiculous! I don't feel guilty for her failures.
這太荒謬了 她不爭氣我並未感到自責
-You think I'm a failure? -lsn't he good?
-你認為我不爭氣? -他不錯吧
Yeah. No,that's not what I was saying.
我不是那個意思?
I thought you were on my side.
多年來我以為你支持我
But maybe you sucked up to them so they'd favor you.
但或許你婚姻失敗目的是想巴結爸媽 讓他們更心疼你
I married a lesbian to make you look good!
我娶女同志是想讓你建立自信
You're right. I mean,you're right.
你說得對.我說,你說得對
It wasn't just the Weebles, but the Weeble Play Palace...
那不是「威伯」的問題 而是威伯遊樂宮
...and the Weeble's Cruise Ship...
和威伯游輪的問題
...with this lifeboat for the Weebles to wobble in.
它上面的救生艇讓威伯能緩緩駛出
And Mom just gave them all away.
偏偏媽媽把他們都給出去了
That's tough,tough stuff.
那滋味不好受
Pheebs,we're gonna catch that movie, we gotta go.
菲比,如果想看電影我們現在該走了
-Feel better. -We're gonna be late,sweetie.
-打起精神來,瑞秋 -菲比,我們快來不及了
-Thanks for everything,Mon. -No problem.
-謝謝你做的一切,摩妮卡 -不客氣
Listen,it was great seeing you again.
各位,很高興和各位再度見面
Mon,easy on those cookies,okay?
摩妮卡,餅乾別吃太多
Remember,they're just food, they're not love.
切記,那只是食物,不是愛
I hate that guy!
我討厭這傢伙
Good night,you guys.
晚安,各位
Oh,look. It's the woman we ordered.
這是我們訂的女人
Hey,can we help you?
需要幫忙嗎?
No,thanks. I'm just waiting for Joey Tribbiani.
不用,謝謝,我在等喬依
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
我就是喬依
Oh,no,not you. Big Joey. Oh,my God!
不是你,是老喬依,天啊
You're so much cuter than your pictures.
你此照片上帥多了
I'm Ronni.
我是羅妮
Cheese Nip?
想吃起司塊(夾子)嗎?
Joey's having an embolism, but I'd go for a nip.
喬伊有「栓子」,我要個「夾子」
Most people, when their pets pass on...
大部份人在寵物過世後
...want them like they're sleeping.
希望它們就像長眠一樣
Occasionally you get a person who wants them in a pose.
但有些人要他們擺出姿勢
Like chasing their tail.
像追自己的尾巴
Or jumping to catch a Frisbee.
跳起接住飛盤
Joey,if I go first, I wanna be looking for my keys.
喬伊,如果我先走 我的姿勢要像找鑰匙一樣
-That's a good one! -Hey.
-這姿勢不錯! -嗨!
Hey,Dad. Ronni's here.
嗨,爸爸.羅妮來了
-Hi. -Hey.
-嗨 -嘿
Hello,babe! What are you doing here?
寶貝,你來幹什麼?
Oh,you left your hair at my place.
你的假髮留在我的住處
I thought you'd need it tomorrow.
我想你明天用得上
Thank you.
謝謝
So,who's up for a big game of Kerplunk?
誰想玩「科普朗克」?
Look,I shouldn't have come.
我不該來這兒
I better go. I'll miss the train.
我該走了,我不想錯過最後一班地鐵
-I don't want you taking that thing. -Where do I stay? Here?
-不,我不要你坐這麼晚的車 -我要住哪兒?這裡?
We'll go to a hotel.
我們去住飯店
-No,you won't. -No,we won't.
-不行 -不行
If you go to a hotel, you'll be doing stuff.
你們去飯店就一定會辦事
I want you here so I can keep an eye on you.
我要你們待在這兒,這樣我就可以監視
-You're gonna keep an eye on us? -Right.
-你要監視我們 -沒錯
As long as you are under my roof...
只要住在我家
...you're gonna live by my rules.
—切就得聽我的
That means no sleeping with your girlfriend.
那就是不准你們睡在一起
Wow,he's strict.
他好嚴格
Dad,you'll be in my room. You can stay in Chandler's room.
爸,你睡我房間 羅妮,你睡錢德的房間
And Chandler will be?
那錢德呢?
Out here with me,bunking up.
在這和我一起,輪船舖位
Oh,bunking up. If you smell s'mores, don't be alarmed.
輪船舖位.如果問到煙味 不要拉警報哦
Thanks. You're a good kid.
謝謝,你真是個好孩子
I'll show you to my room.
我帶你去看我房間
That sounds weird not followed by, "No,it's late."
感覺真奇怪 你沒說「不,謝了,時候不早了」
This is just for tonight. Tomorrow you gotta change.
只有今晚,明天你們就得做出改變
Change?
改變?
-Break up with Ronni -I can't!
-和羅妮分手 -我不能!
Then come clean with Ma! This is not right!
不然就是向媽自首,這樣是不對的
I don't wanna hear it! Now go to my room!
對,但是…我不想聽,快進我房裡
Hey,kickie!
別踢了
-What are you doing? -Getting comfortable.
-你在幹什麼? -找尋舒適的位置
-I can't sleep in my underwear. -Well,you're gonna.
-穿著內褲我睡不著 -你非穿不可
I was thinking about how I'm always seeing girls on top of girls....
我一直在想… 我總是看見女人疊在女人上面
Are they end-to-end, or tall,like pancakes?
她們是首尾相接,還是是像煎餅一樣疊起來
You know,how I date all these women.
懂我意思嗎? 我總想像自己和所有這些女人約會
I always figured,when the right one comes along...
因為我總想夢中情人出現時
... I'll be able to go the distance.
我就會勇往直前,堅持到最後
Now I'm looking at my dad,thinking
但如今看見我爸…看起來
You're not him,you're you.
你不是他,你是你自己
When they wanted you in your father's business,did you cave?
當全天下都希望你繼承你爸的事業時 你有屈服嗎?
-No. -No.
-No.-No.-沒有.-沒有
You chose the out-of-work-actor business.
你決心從事沒有工作的演員事業
That wasn't easy,but you did it.
這不是一件容易的事,但你辦到了
I believe when the right woman comes along...
我也相信夢中情人出現時
...you'll have the guts to say, "No,thanks,I'm married."
你會有勇氣對她說「抱歉,我已婚」
-You really think so? -Yeah,I really do.
-你真的這樣認為? -真的
-Thanks,Chandler. -Get off!
-謝謝,錢德 -滾開
-Hi. -Hi. May I help you?
-Hi -有事嗎?
Joey said I could use your shower since Chandler's in ours.
喬伊說我能用你的浴室 因為錢德正在用我們的
Okay. Who are you?
ok.你是誰?
Oh,I'm Ronni. Ronni Rapalono.
我叫羅妮. 羅妮.拉帕羅羅
The mistress?
情婦
-Come on in. -Thanks.
-請進 -謝謝
I'm Rachel. Bathroom's there.
我叫瑞秋.浴室在那兒
Ronni,how long has Chandler been in the shower?
羅妮,錢德進浴室多久了?
Oh,like five minutes.
約5分鐘
Perfect.
太好了
Fasten your seat belts, it's pee-pee time.
請繫好安全帶,「小弟弟」時間到了
-Hey,Mr. Trib. -Hey,good morning,dear.
-崔先生 -早安
Chandler Bing, it's time to see your thing.
錢德,該我看你的小弟弟了
-What's with you? -I thought it was Chandler!
-你是怎麼搞的?  -我以為你是錢德
You were supposed to be in there so I'd see your thing!
你應該在浴室 這樣我才能看見你的小弟弟
Sorry,my thing was in there with me.
抱歉,我的小弟弟和我在那兒
-How's it going? -Good.
-如何? -不錯
Roger's having a dinner thing. He wanted me to invite you guys.
羅傑想邀大家一起吃晚餐
-So,what's going on? -Nothing.
-怎麼了? -沒事
It's just....
只是…
It's Roger,you know?
羅傑,我說不上來
There's something about
有些事…
We just feel that he's....
基本上我們認為他…
-We hate that guy! -We hate him!
-我們討厭他… -我們討厭他…
-We're sorry,Pheebs. -Okay.
-菲此,我們很抱歉 -ok
Don't you think it's just that he's so perceptive...
是不是他觀察入微
...it freaked you out?
反而嚇到你們了
No,we hate him!
不,我們討厭他…
I'm sorry.
抱歉
-Ma! What are you doing here? -I came to give you this and this!
-媽,你來幹什麼? -我拿這個來給你,還有這個
Big ring!
大戒指!
Why'd you fill your father's head with garbage...
你為什麼要對你爸講一大堆
...about making things right?
關於改正的垃圾呢?
Things were fine this way!
何不順其自然呢?
There's chicken in there. Put it away.
裡面有雞肉,拿去放好
For God's sake,Joey! Really.
拜託,喬依,真的
-Hold on. You knew? -Of course I knew. What do you think?
-慢著,你都知道? -我當然知道,你認為呢?
Your father is no James Bond.
你爸又不是詹姆士龐德
You should've heard his stories.
你應該聽過他的謊言
"I'm sleeping over at my accountant's."
「我在會計這兒睡」
-What is that? Please! -So then,how could you?
-那是什麼?拜託 -你怎能…
Do you remember how your father used to be?
記得你爸以前的模樣嗎?
Always yelling. Nothing made him happy.
總是大吼大叫,總是不開心
Not that wood shop,not those stupid little ships in the bottle.
連木店和瓶內的小船也無法讓他開心
Now he's happy. I mean,it's nice. He has a hobby.
這樣也好,他總算有個嗜好
Ma,I don't mean to be disrespectful...
媽,恕我直言
... but what the hell are you talking about?
你到底在說什麼?
-I mean,what about you? -Me? I'm fine.
-我是說,你怎麼樣? -我很好啊
Look,honey,in an ideal world...
在理想的世界中沒有她
...there'd be no her and your father would look like Sting.
沒有她,你爸也長得和史汀一樣帥
And something else:
再告訴你別的
Ever since that poodle-stuffer came along...
自從那女人出現後
... he's so ashamed of himself that he's been more attentive.
他感到內疚而開始對我體貼
He's been more loving. It's like every day is our anniversary.
每天都像我們的結婚紀念日
-I'm happy for you? -Well,don't be!
-我該為你高興? -不需要
Now everything's screwed up.
因為現在全搞砸了
I just want it the way it was.
我只想回到從前
Ma,I'm sorry.
媽,對不起
I just did what I thought you'd want.
我自以為做了你想做的事
I know you did,cookie. I know you did.
我知道,親愛的,我知道
So tell me. Did you see her?
告訴我,你看見她沒?
Yeah.
看到了
-You're 10 times prettier than she is. -That's sweet.
-你比她漂亮十倍都不止 -嘴巴真甜
Could I take her?
我鬥得過她?
With this ring,no contest.
你有戒指,她鬥不過的
Oh,no! Don't ever do that!
oh,不!永遠不要這樣做!
-What? -I'm sorry.
-什麼? -對不起
I have a thing, which means you can't ever do that!
我有一樣東西, 意味著你永遠不要這麼做
-What's wrong,sweetie? -Nothing.
-怎麼了? -沒事
-No,what's wrong? Come on. -Okay.
-到底怎麼了?快說嘛 -ok
It's nothing. I'm fine. It's just It's my friends.
好吧,我…沒事 問題出在我朋友身上
They have a liking problem with you...
他們對你有意見
...in that they don't.
他們…
They don't?
They don't? 他們?
But they don't see all the wonderfulness that I see.
他們看不見你的好處
They don't see all the good and sweet stuff.
他們看不見你好的一面
-They think you're a little -What?
-他們認為你有點… -什麼?
Intense and creepy.
難以相處
-Oh. -But I don't. Me,Phoebe.
-oh -但我菲比不這麼認為
-I'm not at all surprised about that. -That's why you're so great.
-我對他們的反應毫不感到驚訝. -這就是我欣賞你的地方
It's quite typical behavior...
當群體動力失調時
...when you have this kind of dysfunctional group dynamic.
這是很平常的反應
You know,this kind of codependent, emotionally stunted...
這種相互依賴,情緒激動
...sitting in your stupid coffeehouse, with your stupid big cups...
坐在那家爛咖啡屋, 拿著又大又蠢的咖啡杯
...which might as well have nipples on them.
或許還有乳頭在上面
And you're all like, "Oh,define me! Define me!
你們都會說「定義我這個人」
Love me! I need love!
愛我,我需要愛
You talked to your dad?
你和你爸談過了?
He's gonna keep cheating on Ma like she wanted.
他要以我媽希望的方式繼續欺騙我媽
Ma will keep pretending she doesn't know.
我媽要繼續假裝她一無所知
And my sister,Tina, can't see her husband.
我妹蒂娜不能再見她丈夫
He got a restraining order.
因為他接到禁制令
Which has nothing to do with it. I found out today.
這兩件事沒關係,但我今天才聽說
Things have changed here on Waltons'mountain.
沃頓山這兒的事全變了
-So,Joey,are you okay? -Yeah,I guess.
-喬伊,你沒事吧? -或許吧
It's just You know,they're parents.
他們是…父母
After a certain point, you gotta let go.
你不得不順其自然,即使你知道這樣做不對
You gotta let them make their own mistakes.
但你還是得讓他們犯自己的錯誤
And think,in a few years, we'll turn into them.
而且幾年後我們就和他們一樣
Oh,please.
拜託
If I turn into my parents,I'll be an alcoholic blond chasing men...
如果我像他們一樣 我不是變成追逐金髮帥哥的酒鬼
...or I'll end up like my mom!
就是變得和我媽一樣
-Hey. -Hey,Pheebs.
-嗨 -嗨.菲比
How's it going?
怎麼樣?
Okay,except I broke up with Roger.
還好,只是我和羅傑分手了
-Yeah,right. -No,no,really.
-沒錯 -不…真的
-What happened? -I don't know. I mean...
-怎麼了? -我說不上來
... he's a good person, and he can be really sweet.
他是個好人而且對我很體貼
In some ways, I think he is so right for me.
他的某些方面很適合我
It's just.... I hate that guy!
只是…我討厭這個人
Hi,Joey. What's going on?
Hi,喬伊.怎麼樣?
Clear the tracks for the boobie payback.
為胸脯債務清理跑道
Next stop,Rachel Greene.
下一站,瑞秋.格林
Joey,what the hell were you doing?
喬伊,你在幹什麼?
Sorry,wrong boobies!
對不起,錯誤的胸脯!
Hello,Joey!
喬伊!
Hello,dear!
親愛的!